I'll start off with
with with a welcome back and
congratulations coming back on a second
year here. What what was it that um
kind of made the decision for you or
helped you make the decision to come
back for a second year?
Um I think
what is the word? Familiarity is
probably the easiest way uh way to put
it. I think um
kind of already be like knowing the
defense and being able to just jump
right in and have like I don't want to
say like somewhat of a head start on
learning and things like that is
probably one thing and I feel like
there was somewhat of a belief in me and
my belief in in the team and what I've
what I believe we'll be able to do this
year
will probably be for starters and just I
mean I like the guys there and I'm just
I guess just blessed to have another
opportunity to keep playing this
beautiful game that we play.
How was that that belief in you
demonstrated to you?
Um
like from the team? Yeah.
Um I would say here that that's a I
would I would say that's look that's
kind of a tough question. I would say
the main part is like
um
just like the chance to come back and
play. I think a lot of times like when
teams like cuz I I've played for a few
teams and when teams don't necessarily
know what you're about they ask you to
come work out kind of like I did last
off season when I came in and worked out
with the team. So I would say that would
be not having to work out this year like
just signing a contract and you know
going into the off season would be for
starters and just conversations I've had
with the coaches knowing that what I'm
able to do and what they what they see
me as possibility being able to do this
year you know helping out like different
positions and things like that. So that
that's probably what I would what I
would be able to say just whatever I'm
able to do on special teams or you know
backing up this position or that
position just being able to to fill a
spot if wherever I'm needed.
Did you expect um
you know I guess to either come back or
or to land with the team this earlier or
were you kind of preparing that you'd
have to work out for someone again and
kind of go last year's route? Ooh that's
a good question. I think
um
you kind of always have to expect the
unexpected
with this business. I think there's
there's so many things that go your way
and so many things that don't go your
way. So I think
I didn't necessarily expect to sign back
this early but I'm glad that I did and
I'm I'm I'm ready for uh to get back out
there for OTAs and uh
and be there with the team.
We get the chance to see you guys in the
locker room all the time throughout the
season but for for folks that don't get
the chance to see that how would you
describe the camaraderie of the team?
Uh
now or from like like from this past
season? And probably just from last
season and and maybe maybe a little bit
about you know how you expect that to to
remain going into this year. Yeah I
definitely expect it to to remain the
exactly how it was last season. I think
we I mean it it's always tough. I think
we all play this game to win. We all
play this game to win games to win the
Super Bowl obviously and things like
that but
through the ups and downs of the season
obviously we had a good amount of downs
last season but through the ups and
downs of the season of
season last year I think we found ways
to
to still stay close and still have fun
with it even though we weren't getting
the outcome we wanted each weekend. So I
definitely expect that to
if not stay the same even grow even more
this next season just because I think we
have a lot of belief in what we'll be
able to do this year. So yeah no I
definitely think that the camaraderie
and the guys in the locker room will be
able to gel even more and it will
definitely help us play even better.
Have you been on a team before where
you've had to replace like a
kind of like a locker room giant like
DeMario leaving this year for instance
like
um you know have you have you had that
happen and what kind of has to go right
for that to actually be like a
successful transition? Um
I don't know necessarily if I've been on
a team where we've had a veteran of I'd
say DeMario stature that has left.
Um
and like we've had to like kind of fill
his role if that makes sense. Um I
remember my rookie after my rookie
season when John Johnson left and went
to the the Cleveland Browns we had to
like cuz he was kind of he's like a a
locker room guy great dude as a whole.
So I think him being similar to DeMario
I guess at that time he was only in year
four going in the year five and
DeMario's what going in the 13 14?
I don't know exactly what it is but no I
haven't
yeah I don't know exactly what year he's
going into but I haven't necessarily
been in a situation like that but you
know I wish him the best of luck in in
New York or Jersey for that or whatever
that is and
I I'm sure we'll we'll find a way to to
figure it out.
Um you guys for for the most part are
bringing back almost every piece in that
safety room. I know there's a couple or
I know there's a couple of question
marks still left there but you know just
what what do you what do you see in that
safety room with you and Julian and uh
Jonas uh Julian coming back all that
like what do you just see going into
another year with that that group
together?
Um I definitely see like we were just
talking about camaraderie. Um I think
all season being able to be in the
meeting rooms being able to practice
together with Jay Reed and even even
Elliott. I think as a whole we'll be
we'll be really gelled together and I
think there's a lot of versatility in
the room. I think
almost probably everybody in the room
could play both I mean we don't really
play like free and strong safety we kind
of play right and left but I think
everybody can play everything everybody
can cover in the room. There's a lot of
versatility. Some
multiple guys can play nickel as well if
they're if we're called upon. So I think
uh as a whole we're we're pretty pretty
tight group and I think
uh it'll definitely help us for this
next season and for a couple guys being
their second year in the defense it'll
definitely help everything move a lot
more smoother.
If that makes sense.
>> is that approach of playing right and
left rather than free and strong?
Um I think from a defensive side of the
ball it's nice. I think if I was on the
offensive side playing quarterback
obviously a lot of the quarterbacks in
the NFL are really smart but as the
offensive side of the ball being able to
see two high safeties and not
necessarily know which one's coming down
to cover is definitely I would say an
advantage for the defense because you're
able to disguise different coverages and
things like that and allow
uh quarterbacks to get scrambled a
little bit before the play starts.
Hey Terrell I I I don't know if this is
uh
anything you have personal experience
with in the NFL but um but just with the
way y'all ended last season but do you
think you think that sort of thing can
carry over like good vibes you know
feeling good about where you're headed
despite kind of the
the overall success not being where you
wanted it to be last year?
Yes I think
um not necessarily me but I think
individually in life if uh you have
somebody
like if you're able to gain confidence
from whether somebody believing you or
you doing something uh over and over
again it allows you to propel to to keep
going forward. So I think as a team I
think us being able to what we won five
of our last six
six games last season. I think that'll
that'll carry over into the off season
and into the season allowing us to know
that what we're able to do in this in in
this league and being able to to win a
few more games from the from the
beginning than we did last year.
Terrell could you go could you go back
to when you won the Super Bowl there
with the Rams? What was that like for
you throughout the the course of the
season?
Um
throughout the course of this I I that
is that is one of those one of those
things in life that you'll never ever
forget. I think
um thinking back to that whole season
that whole year that we had in LA I
think uh
as a whole like I was just talking about
how we were really we were really close
team. I think a lot of guys we hung out
a lot outside of the outside of the
facility as well as obviously in the
facility and it just kind of propelled
us to be able to win the Super Bowl. We
had a we had a I think we were seven and
one and then I think in November we had
like a three game stretch where we lost
three in a row. It was like the Niners
the Titans and somebody else and I think
I remember a lot of the media during
that time were like saying like oh this
team has so many players on their team
and they're they're doing this and
they're going downhill.
But for you know we found a way to to
band together and then we won like our
next five and then lost I think the last
game of the season against the Niners
and it was kind of like it's it's now or
never. This is a this is an opportunity
for us to to to win the Super Bowl. So I
remember when Von Miller came to the
team when he had got traded there he had
put his Lombardi trophy in the in the
middle of the locker room and he said
everybody come around and touch it uh
because this is what we're shooting for
and I took it upon myself to not touch
the trophy because I wanted to be able
to
to you know touch our own trophy and I
remember once we ended up winning the
game you know tears were shedding and
things like that but it was uh it was
just a great journey as a whole, and I'm
uh hoping that we get a chance to to
I I get a chance to
feel those feelings again, and uh we get
a chance to, you know, make a run this
year.
So, how much has that helped you out in
your NFL career, winning that Super
Bowl, and seeing yourself as a different
player than when you came into the
league?
Um I would say
it just helped me from a perspective a
uh like a a perception point.
Um being able to see what it is like to
do that, and knowing, I guess, I This
sounds pretty cliché, but like
knowing what it takes to get to that
point. Um it had I think it allows me to
help other guys that haven't been there,
or like young guys coming into the
league, knowing
um what it took for us to get there, and
different like even Justin Reed, he went
to three Super Bowls in a row when he
was in Kansas City, and just having that
knowledge of like the playoff knowledge,
and knowing what it takes to to win
games, cuz each each week it's it's it's
tough to win a game in the NFL. So, just
knowing what it takes to to continue to
win, and getting to that point, I think
it allows me to
have a different perspective on things,
and allow me to help other guys
allow us all to get on the same page, if
that makes sense.
Earl, how has um
Brandon's daily evolved since that Super
Bowl year, and then, you know, you're
working with him so many years later?
Um
I think
I think uh from my rookie year till like
even till last year, I think there's
been a few things that have changed like
within the intricacies of the defense,
but I think from him going from being a
DC to then he left and was the the
Chargers head coach and things like that
till now, I think he's had some ebbs and
flows. I think he did did well, and then
obviously with things like it it ending
in with the Chargers, but I think um as
far as the defense, I would say there's
a few things like within the within the
play calling that has changed a little
bit, but I think he the person he is,
and like the
excellence that he demands, I think has
been the same. I think he's always
demanded excellence among his players,
and I think that's what helps a lot of
people in his system play very well, if
that makes sense.
I keep saying if that makes sense. I I
don't
>> [laughter]
>> You're good. I say that all the time.
Uh
and then just just on that, too, last
year the defense really ascended all
throughout the year, just kind of got
better and better each week. Uh what do
you all feel What do you feel like
that group learned about itself last
year, and how does that impact going
into so many of you going into a second
year together in the system?
I think with anything in life,
um
things will be able to things will work
out if you find a way to trust it. And
I'm not saying that we as a whole as a
whole defense didn't trust it at the
beginning of the season, but I think
like the trust just started to grow
among the players, among the coaches,
and it allowed the defense to to ascend,
and obviously the offense as as a team
as the season went on. So,
um
yeah, I would just say like just the
trust in in the play calling, and in the
system allowed us to just continue to
grow, and continue to
do what we can to help the team win.